Alexis Heroin

Email: alexis.heroin@outlook.com

LinkedIn: <u>alexis-heroin</u> Phone: (437) 849-1638 Location: Toronto, ON

Personal Summary

I am a software developer with 5 years of experience. Throughout the various projects I have worked on, I have developed strong teamwork, collaboration, and communication skills.

Over the past year, I transitioned into the role of tech lead, where I gained experience in team management, providing support, and driving project success.

I am highly motivated to learn new technologies and share my expertise. I believe I can be a valuable asset for the team and ensuring high-quality deliverables within deadlines.

I am eager to discuss further opportunities!

Work Experience

Python Developer • 09/2023 - Now

Givex, Toronto, ON

Worked in the Givex core team to create and maintain features for the back office. Now developing new features on the POS application (20 people team).

Angular Developer • 06/2022 - 06/2023

onepoint, Bordeaux, France

Developed the front-end application using Angular for the 'Provoly' smart city project (20 people team).

Angular and Python Full Stack Developer ● 09/2021 - 06/2022

onepoint, Bordeaux, France

Developed an application using Django and Angular to manage employee staffing across various projects (5 people team).

Laravel API Developer • 09/2019 - 09/2021

onepoint, Bordeaux, France

Developed the game engine and CI/CD pipeline for the serious game project 'Gamabu' for thousands of players (15 people team).

React and Node.js Full Stack Developer • 01/2019 - 03/2019

onepoint, Bordeaux, France

Developed an HR application to help the assignment to missions based on skills and travel time (5 people team).

Education

Master's Degree, Expert in Computer Science and Information Systems ● 2020 - 2022

EPSI, Bordeaux, France Coop training course.

Bachelor's Degree, Application Developer Designer • 2019 - 2020

EPSI, Bordeaux, France Coop training course.

BTS SIO, 2-year French national post-secondary diploma • 2017 - 2019

EPSI, Bordeaux, France

Skills

- PHP (Laravel, Symfony)
- React / Angular
- Python
- JAVA
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- SQL
- Gitlab CI/CD
- Docker and AWS

Languages

- French Native language
- English Fluent

References

Portfolio: https://alexis-heroin.ca
Flags: https://flags.alexis-heroin.ca
Github: https://github.com/Malzik
Gamabu: https://www.gamabu.com
Provoly: https://www.provoly.com